[{"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b92f", "question": "What yard line must a football team drive to, to reach the \"red zone\"?", "answer": "The 20", "category": "general"}, {"id": "60121c4463c99d48cd169b14", "question": "What was the subject of most Norman Rockwell paintings?", "answer": "Everyday life -- His images captured not only the events of daily life, but what they meant to people of the time.", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f031133958d", "question": "What song did Wayne and Garth listen to on their way to the doughnut shop in the movie \"Wayne's World\"?", "answer": "Bohemian Rhapsody", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311339086", "question": "What form of verse is \"Paradise Lost\" written in?", "answer": "Blank verse", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5ff0af73e662d71a53650fbd", "question": "Who is the only poet to win four Pulitzer Prizes?", "answer": "Robert Frost", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c023", "question": "In what city was fashion designer Gianni Versace killed?", "answer": "Miami Beach", "category": "general"}, {"id": "58ab94c586faa38a764be510", "question": "Who bought the rights to manufacture the Isetta in the 1950\u2019s from the Italian company Iso?", "answer": "BMW", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f03113390d1", "question": "What year did Robert Burns write the poem \"Auld Lange Syne\"?", "answer": "1788", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339d35", "question": "Who's responsible for performing \"The Ballad of The Green Berets\"?", "answer": "Barry Sadler", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339d49", "question": "What actress shaved her head for her role in the movie \"Tank Girl\"?", "answer": "Lori Petty", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133bf4a", "question": "What is the last event in a decathlon?", "answer": "1500 Metres", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133bd84", "question": "What type of animal is the Japanese monster, Gezora?", "answer": "Cuttlefish", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338b4f", "question": "Who was the son of Zeus and Maia?", "answer": "Hermes", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5ede129f031133cad0", "question": "What does a nephologist study?", "answer": "Clouds", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b871", "question": "What prominent facial feature is Hello Kitty missing?", "answer": "Mouth", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c3a3", "question": "What three-letter word means the smallest piece of information used by a computer?", "answer": "Bit", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338a0b", "question": "What musical is based on the trials of murderesses Beulah Annan and Belva Gaertner?", "answer": "Chicago", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b8c1", "question": "Coq au vin is a dish made with which type of meat?", "answer": "Chicken", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133be52", "question": "Perfecto, torpedo, and parejo are all shapes of what?", "answer": "Cigars", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a359", "question": "What is the northernmost Scandinavian country?", "answer": "Norway", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339af0", "question": "Who was the first person to say the words \"Live from New York, it's Saturday Night!\"?", "answer": "Chevy Chase", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c3a6", "question": "What land animal has the longest gestation period?", "answer": "The elephant", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133bbdc", "question": "What is the name of the Cheeto's Cheetah?", "answer": "Chester", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c471", "question": "What computer programming language is often referred to by coders as \"Camel\"?", "answer": "Perl", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b3be", "question": "What year was Theodore Roosevelt born in?", "answer": "1858", "category": "history"}, {"id": "58ab956686faa38a764be515", "question": "The Australian auto manufacturer, Holden, is a subsidiary of which US automotive brand?", "answer": "General Motors", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133ac36", "question": "By the end of the 20th Century, what war saw the most Americans die?", "answer": "The US Civil War", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a452", "question": "In what part of the former Soviet Union did the Chernobyl nuclear disaster occur?", "answer": "Ukraine", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd58de129f031133898a", "question": "Which Dickens character asked for more?", "answer": "Oliver Twist", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "59029ef1cad1ec93f27df759", "question": "Above 5,000 ft, coffee beans tend to develop a high level of what?", "answer": "Acidity", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339696", "question": "What is Cartman's first name on the TV show \"South Park\"?", "answer": "Eric", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5fe8b13901dd7bf43be5e791", "question": "Which of the two reindeer are named after weather events?", "answer": "Donner and Blitzen", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5fec8c23ec223966ae8f8846", "question": "In 2000, which artist(s) tied Michael Jackson's 1984 record of winning eight Grammys in a single year?", "answer": "Santana (won eight Grammy Awards in 2000, tying the record set by Michael Jackson)", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "6015ddd1fe83fe1f2a824b64", "question": "Who invented the color wheel?", "answer": "Sir Isaac Newton", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133bb30", "question": "What is your occupation if you are sometimes referred to as an apiarist?", "answer": "Beekeeper", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133bdfd", "question": "Whose famous balloon says \"State Fair Omaha\" on the outside?", "answer": "The Wizard of Oz's", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5fd96e6a23c87fd04dd15e37", "question": "How many instruments could Richard Nixon play?", "answer": "5", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f031133a167", "question": "Who played Sarah Conner in the 1991 film \"Terminator 2: Judgment Day\"?", "answer": "Linda Hamilton", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5f9f4afeaf848b908361b87d", "question": "What is a group of turkeys called?", "answer": "A rafter or flock", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a220", "question": "Which tough guy actor was once a linotype operator?", "answer": "Robert Mitchum", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b1cd", "question": "What did Pieter van Musschenbroek create at a namesake Dutch university in 1746 by lining a glass jar with silver foil?", "answer": "The Leyden jar", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338f6e", "question": "What can be a font, architectural style or novel type?", "answer": "Gothic", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133bce0", "question": "What fashion brand was co-founded by artist Bono?", "answer": "Edun", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a5f4", "question": "Which US state is known as the \u201cLand of Enchantment\u201d?", "answer": "New Mexico", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a467", "question": "What city is the capital of the US state of New Mexico?", "answer": "Santa Fe", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f031133a09e", "question": "Susanne and Joanne Catherall sang with which band?", "answer": "The Human League", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339d87", "question": "What famous rapper's real name is Calvin Broadus?", "answer": "Snoop Dogg", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5ede129f031133c91f", "question": "Which fish, previously thought to be extinct was rediscovered In 1939?", "answer": "The Coelacanth", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5f9f485baf848b908361b878", "question": "How many black keys are found on a traditional 88-key piano?", "answer": "36", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5fe1f2e9145fb29466707398", "question": "What was the world's first digital quartz watch called?", "answer": "The Pulsar", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5ede129f031133cb08", "question": "Which planet is orbited by the moon Charon?", "answer": "Pluto", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c60b", "question": "What is the fear of washing or bathing called?", "answer": "Ablutophobia", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5db03f44aa1c9af2684d79a6", "question": "Who was the mother of the Minotaur?", "answer": "Pasipha\u00eb", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c793", "question": "What part of the cheetah does not have any spots?", "answer": "The belly", "category": "science"}, {"id": "59cdb2dc65ff7d326b622a7a", "question": "Which Apollo space mission put the first men on the moon?", "answer": "Apollo 11", "category": "history"}, {"id": "596dfbe79616e6c6d4eba4f0", "question": "What animal can you smell a mile away?", "answer": "The skunk", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5fecd3a5ec223966ae8f88c6", "question": "What famous film character says: \"I'm gonna make him an offer he can't refuse\"?", "answer": "Vito Corleone", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5feba9067e83c707845b20d0", "question": "A computer opponent's ability to adaptively challenge a player is known as what?", "answer": "Artificial intelligence (AI)", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133bfea", "question": "Is kissing under the mistletoe comes from whose customs?", "answer": "Druids", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5fec8d52ec223966ae8f8851", "question": "Which actor voices Miles Morales in \"Into the Spider-Verse\"?", "answer": "Shameik Moore", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "59a552683e1c6f9840ba3195", "question": "Where was the Armistice of 11 November 1918 signed?", "answer": "Compiegne", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a3f3", "question": "Which pass connects Afghanistan to Pakistan?", "answer": "The Khyber Pass", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339d84", "question": "What time-travel film was shot on Michigan's three-mile-long Mackinac Island?", "answer": "Somewhere in Time", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b490", "question": "Which country were the 1988 Winter Olympic Games held in?", "answer": "Canada", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133bf6f", "question": "What are described by the terms rep, challis and foulard?", "answer": "Neckties", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f03113396c6", "question": "Who voiced the character of Woody in the Toy Story movie series?", "answer": "Tom Hanks", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a8eb", "question": "What bay is actually the United States' largest tidal estuary?", "answer": "Chesapeake Bay", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "59e6bcdcfb6c85e9e634ff61", "question": "What's the capital of Senegal?", "answer": "Dakar", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5b358a735db0d66a186cb553", "question": "What is the birth name of actress Paula Prentiss?", "answer": "Paula Ragusa", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5fe6a81c20565ad31a57c7f3", "question": "What children's author also invented a surgical device?", "answer": "Roald Dahl", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5bfdfeacb668d7dfe168b5b0", "question": "The term \"lupine\" refers to which animal?", "answer": "Wolf", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133bd37", "question": "Who scored the famous \"Hand of God\" goal in the 1986 World Cup?", "answer": "Diego Maradona", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a684", "question": "What large US city is located near Lake Mead?", "answer": "Las Vegas", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "6014c8defbde8045e48466e2", "question": "What do plants produce through photosynthesis?", "answer": "Plants use energy from the sun to turn carbon dioxide into food. Carbohydrates and oxygen are the end result of photosynthesis.", "category": "science"}, {"id": "59067c20ff9c0647b50a806a", "question": "What mountain range does the Gotthard Base Tunnel pass through?", "answer": "The Alps", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339964", "question": "In the TV show \"The Simpsons\", before becoming a tavern owner, what was Moe's profession?", "answer": "Boxer", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338e44", "question": "What two-word phrase is the first writing to appear in \"Charlotte's Web\"?", "answer": "Some pig", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "58b373541c3f17ccc40c8e2c", "question": "Shakespeare's \"The Taming of the Shrew\" depicts the courtship of which characters?", "answer": "Petruchio and Katherina", "category": "art"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b02d", "question": "\u201cWhat hath God wrought\u201d was the first message ever sent on what type of a communication device?", "answer": "Telegraph", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c6b2", "question": "The hottest natural chemical according to the Scoville Scale, resiniferatoxin, comes from what plant?", "answer": "Resin spurge", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311339466", "question": "Who played the role of Warden Hal Moores in the 1999 movie \"The Green Mile\"?", "answer": "James Cromwell", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5ede129f031133c925", "question": "What is a characteristic of a \"nimbus\" cloud?", "answer": "Rain", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133be5d", "question": "What is the only US state to boast a radio station whose call letters are the exact same name of the city?", "answer": "Waco", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f03113397b5", "question": "What trumpeter is considered the pioneer of cool jazz?", "answer": "Miles Davis", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "6003952057a0e35c43f83892", "question": "Any color plus black is called what?", "answer": "A shade", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f03113396c7", "question": "What baseball team did Cheers' manager Sam Malone play for in the TV show?", "answer": "The Boston Red Sox", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133af4f", "question": "During the 20th Century, in what year did the annexation of Austria by German take place?", "answer": "1938", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd58de129f0311338993", "question": "Who composed the \"Brandenburg Concertos\"?", "answer": "Johann Sebastian Bach", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133bbc9", "question": "What country's population hit the one billion mark in May 2000?", "answer": "India", "category": "general"}, {"id": "6015ea88fe83fe1f2a824bf1", "question": "What nickname was given to the serial killer, Jack the Ripper?", "answer": "The Whitechapel Murderer", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311339363", "question": "Where did Helen and Joel get married on the TV show \"Wings\"?", "answer": "The bathroom", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c0f2", "question": "A light aircraft without an engine is called a what?", "answer": "Glider or a sailplane", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133bc13", "question": "What year did designer Manolo Blahnik open his first namesakes store in Hong Kong?", "answer": "1991", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f03113399df", "question": "In the 1991 animated Disney film \"Beauty and the Beast\", what type of enchanted item is Chip?", "answer": "A teacup", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5fd66c32a5bfecdd737e0890", "question": "What was the first martial art to use colored belts to signify rank?", "answer": "Judo", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133bf1b", "question": "What was the first artificial flavouring?", "answer": "Vanilla Essence", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133aa9a", "question": "How many stars does the New Zealand national flag have?", "answer": "Four", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339b25", "question": "In 2007, what morning network TV program expanded from three hours to four?", "answer": "The Today Show", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "59a552833e1c6f9840ba3197", "question": "The telephone country code 82 would connect you with which country?", "answer": "South Korea", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5fe1ecd7145fb29466707389", "question": "Where did the first Dunkin' Donuts open?", "answer": "Quincy, Massachusetts", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5a162cf2f01ec323f8491734", "question": "An astronomical unit is the standard measurement taken from the Earth to where?", "answer": "The Sun", "category": "science"}, {"id": "594a62c92ebb971c1417fb93", "question": "What name was given to the fishing dispute between Spain and Canada that lasted from 1994 to 1996?", "answer": "Turbot War", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338f29", "question": "Who wrote \"120 Days of Sodom\" while in prison?", "answer": "The Marquis de Sade", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd58de129f0311338881", "question": "What adventure tale introduced: \"Yo-ho-ho, and a bottle of rum!\"", "answer": "Treasure Island", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133aca6", "question": "Which is the 28th US state?", "answer": "Texas", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5921fd54a4edfd43a087adc9", "question": "How many holes can be found in the standard bowling ball?", "answer": "3", "category": "general"}, {"id": "601b491e49076251badbeaac", "question": "Who said, \"In the future, everyone will be world-famous for 15 minutes\"?", "answer": "Andy Warhol -- There is debate as to whether the phrase is his word, but branded it and put in pamphlet in 1968.", "category": "history"}, {"id": "58f16b8af7c52aae91cc07e8", "question": "What is the meaning of the name of the constellation Ophiuchus?", "answer": "Serpent Bearer", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5fef62056ce05a3942286e5a", "question": "What was Jimi Hendrix's birth name?", "answer": "Johnny Allen Hendrix", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5eb73cea5e259d7869087332", "question": "A \"waltz-length\" dress stops at what part of the body?", "answer": "The calf", "category": "general"}, {"id": "601739db44491cbd7c5a1799", "question": "Who is the first known architect in history?", "answer": "Imhotep -- He designed Egypt\u2019s Pyramid of Djoser in 2630 BC. He also gets credit for using columns before anyone else.", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133bb32", "question": "What supermodel appeared dressed as George Washington on the cover of the premiere issue of \"George\" magazine?", "answer": "Cindy Crawford", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c6aa", "question": "What is the chemical symbol for the element Magnesium on the periodic table?", "answer": "Mg", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338e23", "question": "In what country was Zubin Mehta born?", "answer": "India", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "59ae92ec574a5ce6b56b8233", "question": "What sport is played by the Chicago Bulls?", "answer": "Basketball", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133aafd", "question": "The Volta is the largest river in which country?", "answer": "Ghana", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339e09", "question": "What New York banker did Star Jones marry in 2004?", "answer": "Al Reynolds", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5b323184bf195a31e15d7385", "question": "What cartoon featured a boy with a community of tiny people living in his wall?", "answer": "The Littles", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f03113392d7", "question": "Which singer had a 1964 hit with \"King of the Road\"?", "answer": "Roger Miller", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133bc64", "question": "How many different car models were there in the first Hot Wheels release in 1968?", "answer": "16", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b256", "question": "Which amendment to the US Constitution deals with self-incrimination?", "answer": "Fifth", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c6fc", "question": "What dermatological problem do you most likely have if you have over secreting sebaceous glands?", "answer": "Acne", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5fecd87eec223966ae8f88dd", "question": "Which film's antagonist was nicknamed \"Bruce\" after a Hollywood lawyer?", "answer": "\"Jaws\"", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339c75", "question": "Whose look-alike archenemy was named KARR?", "answer": "KITT's", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b49c", "question": "Which country was selected as a host of the 1916 Olympic Games, but didn't actually host them?", "answer": "Germany", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5ff6679c52a821ff76ae8afe", "question": "Which historical member of British royalty made Christmas trees mainstream there?", "answer": "Prince Albert, the German husband of Queen Victoria", "category": "history"}, {"id": "59008adbcf842fa4c4ba9694", "question": "What is the name of the lively Spanish dance in triple time and typically performed with castanets or tambourines?", "answer": "Fandango", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f03113393ac", "question": "Who plays the role of Kissy Suzuki in the movie \"You Only Live Twice\"?", "answer": "Mie Hama", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b9e9", "question": "On what video game platform did the Gran Turismo game series debut?", "answer": "Playstation", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133aa98", "question": "Which country is also the world's largest archipelago?", "answer": "Indonesia", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b697", "question": "What is a \"major-domo\"?", "answer": "A chief steward", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5b5717d767df192a942e3359", "question": "What significance does the number 4468 have to trainspotters?", "answer": "Marks the 4468 Mallard, the fastest steam locomotive", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5fe69af420565ad31a57c758", "question": "What famous inventor proposed to his wife in Morse Code?", "answer": "Thomas Edison", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5fbaefd00738315b1fb74e33", "question": "Which is the longest English word without a vowel?", "answer": "Nymphly", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5fe8b25401dd7bf43be5e79c", "question": "\"And Bob\u2019s your uncle\" is typically used in which way?", "answer": "Conclude a talking point", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339f81", "question": "What was Billy J. Kramer's backing band?", "answer": "The Dakotas", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b11e", "question": "Who was the second US President to appear on the face of a US coin?", "answer": "George Washington", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b909", "question": "What video game got its name from a Japanese mistranslation of \"King Kong\"?", "answer": "Donkey Kong", "category": "general"}, {"id": "58ab94b786faa38a764be50f", "question": "Who bought the rights to manufacture the Isetta in the 1950\u2019s from the Italian company Iso?", "answer": "BMW", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5ff0b4e1e662d71a53650ff1", "question": "Which of Edgar Allen Poe's works was written in honor of his wife?", "answer": "Annabel Lee", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338b15", "question": "In which decade did the \"Peanuts\" comic strip debut?", "answer": "1950s", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a969", "question": "What California peak, which erupted in 1915, is the world's largest lava dome?", "answer": "Lassen Peak", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c17d", "question": "What is the opposite of an utopia?", "answer": "Dystopia", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5fe4ddaa06d333868d34d706", "question": "During World War II, where was \"Hacksaw Ridge\" located?", "answer": "Okinawa", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b968", "question": "On which wedding anniversary would you buy your partner leather?", "answer": "The 3rd", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c0c5", "question": "What is Frank Whittle credited with inventing?", "answer": "Turbojet engine", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5ede129f031133ca5c", "question": "The flowers of the curry tree are what color?", "answer": "White", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5fe6a97820565ad31a57c804", "question": "Where is the \"grassy knoll\" located?", "answer": "Dealey Plaza, Dallas, Texas", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339d5c", "question": "What song did the Drifters follow with the 1964 sequel \"I've Got Sand in My Shoes\"?", "answer": "Under the Boardwalk", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a652", "question": "Oregon's Mount Hood is located in what mountain chain?", "answer": "Cascade Mountains", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338fb1", "question": "Which author wrote the novel \"The War of the End of the World\"?", "answer": "Mario Vargas Llosa", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f031133963c", "question": "Which Disney's cartoon character's love interest is named Prince Philip?", "answer": "Princess Aurora's", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133bb69", "question": "What tennis player was named \"Sexiest Woman in the World\" by FHM magazine in 2002?", "answer": "Anna Kournikova", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b517", "question": "What is the only alcoholic drink one can buy in the dry Moore county in Tennessee?", "answer": "Jack Daniel's", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133bbd6", "question": "According to legend, what outlaw killed one man for each of the 21 years he lived?", "answer": "Billy the Kid", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5fd6662aa5bfecdd737e0866", "question": "How long are the white dashed lines that divide lanes on U.S. roads?", "answer": "10 feet", "category": "general"}, {"id": "59ca3e1344f0f6af5b066644", "question": "In mathematics which prefix refers to 10 to the power of minus 18?", "answer": "Atto", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133aa15", "question": "What line on a map connects places of equal rainfall?", "answer": "Isohyet", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "6014c8c5fbde8045e48466e0", "question": "Most flowers have an odd number of what?", "answer": "Petals", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339b5c", "question": "Who played Babe Ruth in the 1992 film \"The Babe\"?", "answer": "John Goodman", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338c36", "question": "The Newbery Medal is awarded annually for what genre of writing?", "answer": "Children's literature", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b056", "question": "What famous magician died on Halloween Day in 1926?", "answer": "Harry Houdini", "category": "history"}, {"id": "591c37bc815febcc896f9273", "question": "What is the tenth sign of the Zodiac?", "answer": "Capricorn", "category": "general"}, {"id": "58b8cba894b094db9158309a", "question": "Which Academy Award winner was the executive producer of the 2015 re-cut documentary \"Cowspiracy\"?", "answer": "Leonardo DiCaprio", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5bb35b4f2627b8fe95581beb", "question": "In ABC's \"Once Upon a Time\" what character was played by Colin O' Donoghue?", "answer": "Captain Hook", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5fc991d875534e0fe3fe3c2b", "question": "Who said, \"I don't like to pay for the same real estate twice\"?", "answer": "General George S Patton", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5fe8f40e01dd7bf43be5e81d", "question": "DIY stands for what?", "answer": "Do It Yourself", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133baf5", "question": "What color hair does Sega character Sonic the Hedgehog have?", "answer": "Blue", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5990f96bfa5fdd6dd25324f7", "question": "Who created \"The Scarlet Pimpernel\"?", "answer": "Baroness Orczy", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5feb33fd7e83c707845b20c7", "question": "What actor said, \"If you had been a public figure since the time you were a toddler\u2026 maybe you too would value privacy above all else\"?", "answer": "Jodie Foster", "category": "history"}, {"id": "6015f7b6fe83fe1f2a824c25", "question": "Which Christmas carol became the first song ever to be broadcast from space?", "answer": "Astronauts Tome Stafford and Wally Schirra sang \"Jingle Bells\" from space on 16 December 1965.", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338c6e", "question": "\"Whistler\u2019s Mother\" was the first painting by an American to be displayed at what museum?", "answer": "The Louvre", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a1be", "question": "Lesley Hornby became more famous as who?", "answer": "Twiggy", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5febd4087e83c707845b2158", "question": "Ozzy Osbourne is the former lead vocalist of which classic heavy metal band?", "answer": "Black Sabbath", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd58de129f03113388f1", "question": "What Agatha Christie novel was made up of two parts - England and Egypt?", "answer": "Death on the Nile", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5fe4e16506d333868d34d727", "question": "Who wrote \"The Communist Manifesto\"?", "answer": "Karl Marx and Friedrich Engels", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a5dc", "question": "What are the five boroughs of  New York City?", "answer": "Brooklyn, Queens, The Bronx, Manhattan and Staten Island", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a48b", "question": "In which city is the Prado art gallery located?", "answer": "Madrid", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b9af", "question": "What American fashion designer founded the Polo clothing line?", "answer": "Ralph Lauren", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a688", "question": "Lake Mohave lies several miles south of what larger lake?", "answer": "Lake Mead", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a5d9", "question": "What does the brass plate on Number 10 Downing Street say?", "answer": "First Lord of the Admiralty", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "601b4bc649076251badbeac8", "question": "What was U.S. President Woodrow Wilson's reelection campaign slogan in 1916?", "answer": "\"He Kept Us Out of War\" -- Despite the slogan, he asked Congress to declare war in 1917.", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5e5f11add274615ecf51453a", "question": "In what country was the worlds first ice hotel built?", "answer": "Sweden", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133af61", "question": "Which prison was Nelson Mandela released from?", "answer": "Victor Verster", "category": "history"}, {"id": "59e806b1de59ea584496feb3", "question": "How is \"Albert DeSalvo\" better known?", "answer": "The Boston Strangler", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b73a", "question": "The original Legoland opened in which country in 1968?", "answer": "Denmark", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5fffa6a173838c5c8a417f30", "question": "How many teeth does an aardvark have?", "answer": "None", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133bb2d", "question": "Someone who raises false alarms is said to cry what?", "answer": "Wolf", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5ede129f031133c97b", "question": "Polaris is more commonly referred to as what?", "answer": "The North Star", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133ac49", "question": "What was the nickname of German flying ace Manfred von Richthofen?", "answer": "The Red Baron", "category": "history"}, {"id": "58dba497874c93a3298b2146", "question": "What is believed to have eventually killed Oliver Cromwell?", "answer": "Malaria and urinary/kidney infection", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a791", "question": "What strait connects the Persian Gulf to the Gulf of Oman?", "answer": "Strait of Hormuz", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "6015eaf2fe83fe1f2a824bf6", "question": "Which Native American tribe took part in the first Thanksgiving feast?", "answer": "Wampanoag", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5fe7c829877e98cb977789df", "question": "Which sea lies at one end of the Great Wall of China?", "answer": "The Yellow Sea", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "6015e594fe83fe1f2a824bc1", "question": "In which period did ballet originate?", "answer": "Italian Renaissance", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f031133901f", "question": "Rodin's \"The Thinker\" is believed to be a portrait of what Italian poet?", "answer": "Dante", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133ba16", "question": "What sport's Hall of Fame is located in Cooperstown?", "answer": "Baseball", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f03113394f6", "question": "Which Teletubby has a triangle on its head?", "answer": "Tinky Winky", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b055", "question": "For what crime was Al Capone finally sent to prison for in 1931?", "answer": "Tax evasion", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5b7ab9226490a8cc1a6e528f", "question": "Who was the protagonist in the book \"Fahrenheit 451\"?", "answer": "Guy Montag", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "58b3731c1c3f17ccc40c8e2a", "question": "In \"The Wizard of Oz\", what was the lion in search of?", "answer": "Courage", "category": "art"}, {"id": "5b7ab8a16490a8cc1a6e528d", "question": "In what year was the first Call of Duty game released?", "answer": "2003", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f031133909c", "question": "Demeter is the goddess of what?", "answer": "Harvest and agriculture", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338b4e", "question": "Who wrote \"Gulliver's Travels\"?", "answer": "Jonathan Swift", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338db8", "question": "Who killed Count Rugen?", "answer": "Inigo Montoya", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311339037", "question": "What is non-rhyming poetry called?", "answer": "Blank verse", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339eb9", "question": "Who left his Air America radio show in 2007 to run for the US Senate?", "answer": "Al Franken", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5909cc60bb53d1af658864e0", "question": "On which three days of the week is December 25th more likely to fall?", "answer": "Tuesday, Friday or Sunday", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5cefc136948005ec986edce5", "question": "Who is the twelfth member of the group LOONA to debut?", "answer": "Olivia Hye", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339830", "question": "What movie, directed by the Coen brothers, won an Oscar for \"Best Picture\" in 2008?", "answer": "No Country for Old Men", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b6a6", "question": "Apple's CEO Steve Jobs was known for wearing what color turtleneck?", "answer": "Black", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338ed3", "question": "In what 1952 play is Giles Corey \"pressed\" to death, his last words being \"More weight\"?", "answer": "The Crucible", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "59ae934a574a5ce6b56b8239", "question": "Who was the Greek equivalent of the Roman goddess Juventas?", "answer": "Hebe", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "58f169b5f7c52aae91cc07d3", "question": "Who played \"Hawkeye\" in the 1970 film \"MASH\"?", "answer": "Donald Sutherland", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133ba1a", "question": "What figure did the tobacco company R.J. Reynolds decommission in 1997?", "answer": "Joe Camel", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133bcd9", "question": "What was the only place Tandy's popular TRS-80 computers were sold?", "answer": "RadioShack", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b656", "question": "\"Friends of Bill W.\" is another name for what?", "answer": "Alcoholics Anonymous", "category": "general"}, {"id": "58dba6be874c93a3298b215b", "question": "What is the name of the long pole with a microphone attached at the end on a movie set?", "answer": "A boom", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311339310", "question": "In the movie \"The Shining\", what was the name of the hotel resort?", "answer": "The Overlook Hotel", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133ba95", "question": "Who was the first football coach to win both a Rose Bowl in 1976 and a Super Bowl in 2000?", "answer": "Dick Vermeil", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339b83", "question": "For what 2001 movie did Ron Howard win an Oscar for Best Director?", "answer": "A Beautiful Mind", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311339243", "question": "What is the main character's job in the movie \"Raiders of the Lost Ark\"?", "answer": "Archeologist", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5fea421cff048f679a45ab74", "question": "How many faces are there in an icosahedron?", "answer": "Twenty", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f03113391a1", "question": "Who is known as Slim Shady?", "answer": "Marshall Mathers", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133ae9b", "question": "Who was the first European explorer to sail into New York Bay?", "answer": "Giovanni da Verrazano", "category": "history"}, {"id": "597cd610e347d002c297e4ba", "question": "On what date is The Melbourne Cup traditionally held?", "answer": "The first Tuesday of November", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339c87", "question": "Who has the only speaking part in Mel Brooks' \"Silent Movie\"?", "answer": "Marcel Marceau", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5b3233efbf195a31e15d73a0", "question": "What does a \"kymograph\" measure?", "answer": "Oscillations", "category": "science"}, {"id": "600241ac4be4723ccac2217b", "question": "Which book by Thomas More, published in 1516, depicts an ideal fictional island society?", "answer": "\"Utopia\"", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5fe7c111877e98cb97778971", "question": "Where is the \"Garden of the Sleeping Giant\"?", "answer": "Fiji", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5ede129f031133ca2f", "question": "Laetrile is most often associated with the pit of which fruit?", "answer": "Apricot", "category": "science"}, {"id": "6015eaaafe83fe1f2a824bf2", "question": "Who claimed he could \"drive away the devil with a fart\"?", "answer": "Martin Luther", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f031133a0dd", "question": "Who was Humphrey Bogarts 4th wife?\u00a0", "answer": "Lauren Bacall", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "597cd9cfe347d002c297e4ce", "question": "What became the tallest building in London after its official opening in October 1965?", "answer": "Post Office Tower", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b80b", "question": "What holiday comes right before All Saints' Day?", "answer": "Halloween", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5e93a8c6d6f11f394a3b2d58", "question": "In the manga series \"Bleach\", what is the name of Izura Kira's zanpakuto?", "answer": "Wabisuke", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133ae2d", "question": "Captain James Cook made how many voyages to the Pacific Ocean?", "answer": "3", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5fdd5e060499cffc60b84233", "question": "What Egyptian monster feasts on the heart of someone unworthy of eternal life?", "answer": "Ammut", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a76f", "question": "The Brenner Pass lies on the border of Austria and what other country?", "answer": "Italy", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5c88e61b22f44c2d77a29c3f", "question": "What is Patty's last name in the 1978 film \"Grease\"?", "answer": "Simcox", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5fea43a0ff048f679a45ab84", "question": "What kind of star system is Algol?", "answer": "A binary star system", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5b571bdc67df192a942e336e", "question": "What is the name of the farm in the book \"Animal Farm\"?", "answer": "Manor Farm", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "60136faf138175489539637a", "question": "In 2000, what character was elected U.S. President in the DC universe?", "answer": "Lex Luthor", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f031133994f", "question": "What rock musician was Heather Locklear\u2019s second husband?", "answer": "Richie Sambora", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5fe65c541f3c0ead6880d612", "question": "What was the most important celestial object for the Aztecs?", "answer": "The sun", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338d50", "question": "Author Margaret Atwood hails from what country?", "answer": "Canada", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5fd6a3346c0f9723ab15cb4b", "question": "What was Ronald Reagan\u2019s Secret Service code name?", "answer": "Rawhide", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338a99", "question": "What word becomes shorter by adding two letters to it?", "answer": "Short/small", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5c90d3a052800b05cac20f18", "question": "What planet in our Solar System has the longest day?", "answer": "Venus", "category": "science"}, {"id": "58d06ca9870e6f05ba600854", "question": "Who wrote the novel \"The Moneychangers\"?", "answer": "Arthur Hailey", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a3e5", "question": "What is the capital of Monaco?", "answer": "Monaco", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c2df", "question": "How many pounds of honey is eaten by bees to produce 1 pound of beeswax?", "answer": "8 Pounds", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133ba12", "question": "What US city hosts the annual Gator Bowl?", "answer": "Jacksonville", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133ab5f", "question": "Prague is the capital of which country?", "answer": "Czech Republic", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a7b9", "question": "In which US state is the geographic center of the 48 contiguous states?", "answer": "Kansas", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c7f3", "question": "What animal is \"Artemia salina\"?", "answer": "Brine shrimp", "category": "science"}]